A Guide to the Virginia Room Election Files, 1950-2015
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
The Virginia Room Election Files, 1950-2015
Fairfax County Public Library
24.0 linear feet
The Virginia Room Election Files contain over 950 files of information on the various elections that Fairfax County, City of Fairfax, Vienna, Herndon, and Clifton residents have voted on from 1950 to the present. Coverage is sporadic through the 1950s but files become more consistent beginning in the 1960s. Included are newspaper articles; candidate brochures/pamphlets/booklets/mission statements, etc.; business cards; fans; door tags; stickers; letters and bumper stickers.
Virginia Room staff
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None
Acquisition Information
Collection assembled by Virginia Room staff over a period of years.
Historical and Biographical Information
Virginia Room staff intermittently began collecting election materials in the early 1950s. Beginning in 1960, they maintained files for every year although just a limited number of campaigns received coverage. In the early 1970s, the collection expanded to include more campaigns with the arrival of a full-time Virginia Room Librarian. During this time the Virginia Room actively sought out campaign materials by writing candidates every October requesting literature, campaign brochures and policy statements for reference and handout. Staff duplicated whatever they received and any election coverage they had clipped out from newspapers and sent copies to other library branches in what became known as the Voter Service File.
Over the years the election files have come to be seen as a community service and many candidates have come in to look at the files to see what people had promised when they ran. The intent of the collection has evolved from focusing on a handful of elections to covering all elections that Fairfax County citizens vote on with the exception of Vice-Presidential and Presidential elections. Staff refrained from collecting files on these elections since information on them had been more easily accessible than the local elections. The Virginia Room decided at the end of the 2013 election cycle that they would no longer actively seek out items; however, they will continue to add to the collection as items are donated.
Scope and Content
Many elections are covered in the collection with the exception of Vice-Presidential and Presidential elections. Elections that are covered in the collection (but do not necessarily exist for every year) include: General election information, Bonds/Amendments/Referendums, Board of Supervisors, City/Town Council, Commissioner of Revenue, Mayor, School Board, Sheriff, Soil & Water Conservation, Treasurer, Attorney General, Commonwealth Attorney, Governor, Lieutenant Governor, VA House of Delegates, VA Senate, US House of Representatives, US Senate, Results and Voters’ Guides. If a file folder does not exist for an election you are looking for then you may want to check to see if the “General” folder exists for that specific year and look in that one for the information. The collection covers town elections for the City of Fairfax (previously known as Fairfax City), Clifton, Herndon and Vienna.
The materials contained in the files include: newspaper articles; candidate brochures/pamphlets/booklets/mission statements, etc.; business cards; fans; door tags; stickers; letters and bumper stickers.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
None
None
Index Terms
Election districts-Virginia-Fairfax County; Elections-Virginia-Fairfax County; Fairfax County (Va.)-Politics and government; Voter registration-Virginia-Fairfax County; Voting-Virginia-Fairfax County
Container List
- Bonds, 1950
- Board of Supervisors, 1953
- Virginia House of Delegates, 1953
- General, 1956
- General, 1957
- General, 1960
- Bonds, 1961
- City of Fairfax, 1961
- City of Fairfax, 1962
- General, 1962
- General, 1963
- City of Fairfax, 1964
- General, 1964
- Vienna, 1964
- City of Fairfax, 1965
- General, 1965
- Vienna, 1965
- City of Fairfax, 1966
- Fairfax County, 1966
- U.S. Congress, 1966
- Vienna, 1966
- Board of Supervisors, 1967
- City of Fairfax, 1967
- Clerk of the Court, 1967
- Commonwealth's Attorney, 1967
- General, 1967
- General Candidates Questionnaires, 1967
- Sheriff, 1967
- Virginia House of Delegates, 1967
- Virginia State Senate, 1967
- Vienna, 1967
- City of Fairfax, 1968
- General, 1968
- General Assembly, 1968
- Results, 1968
- U.S. Congress, 1968
- Vienna, 1968
- Voter Registration, 1968
- City of Fairfax, 1969
- General, 1969
- General Assembly, 1969
- Results, 1969
- Virginia House of Delegates - Special Election, 1969
- Vienna, 1969
- Voter Registration, 1969
- Bonds, 1970
- City of Fairfax, 1970
- General, 1970
- General Assembly, 1970
- Results, 1970
- U.S. Congress, 1970
- Vienna, 1970
- Bonds, 1971
- Fairfax County, 1971
- General, 1971
- General Assembly, 1971
- Republican, 1971
- Results, 1971
- Vienna, 1971
- City of Fairfax, 1972
- General, 1972
- General Assembly, 1972
- Results, 1972
- Special Election, 1972
- U.S. Congress, 1972
- Vienna, 1972
- City of Fairfax, 1973
- General, 1973
- General Assembly, 1973
- Results, 1973
- Vienna, 1973
- Bonds, 1974
- City of Fairfax, 1974
- General, 1974
- Results, 1974
- U.S. Congress, 1974
- Vienna, 1974
- Bonds, 1975
- General, 1975
- General Assembly, 1975
- Results, 1975
- Vienna, 1975
- Bonds, 1976
- City of Fairfax, 1976
- General, 1976
- General Assembly, 1976
- Results, 1976
- U.S. Congress, 1976
- Vienna, 1976
- Bonds, 1977
- Fairfax County, 1977
- Primaries, 1977
- Results, 1977
- Vienna, 1977
- Bonds, 1978
- Campaign Financing, 1978
- City of Fairfax, 1978
- General, 1978
- Results, 1978
- Soil and Water Conservation District, 1978
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 1978
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 1978
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th - Primary, 1978
- U.S. House of Representatives - to June Convention, 1978
- U.S. Senate - Convention to November, 1978
- U.S. Senate - to June Convention, 1978
- Vienna, 1978
- Board of Supervisors, 1979
- General, 1979
- Primaries, 1979
- Results, 1979
- Sheriff, 1979
- Virginia House of Delegates, 1979
- Virginia State Senate, 1979
- Vienna, 1979
- Amendments - Constitutional, 1980
- Bonds, 1980
- General, 1980
- Results, 1980
- Spring 1980, 1980
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 1980
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 1980
- U.S. House of Representatives - General, 1980
- Attorney General, 1981
- Bonds, 1981
- Bonds - City of Fairfax, 1981
- City of Fairfax Races, 1981
- Conventions, 1981
- Democrats - General, 1981
- General, 1981
- Governor/Lieutenant Governor, 1981
- Results, 1981
- Virginia House of Delegates - 49th, 1981
- Virginia House of Delegates - 50th, 1981
- Virginia House of Delegates - 51st, 1981
- Virginia House of Delegates - 52nd, 1981
- Virginia House of Delegates - General, 1981
- Amendments - Constitutional, 1982
- Bonds, 1982
- Bonds - Parks, 1982
- Campaign Financing, 1982
- City of Fairfax, 1982
- City of Fairfax - Treasurer, 1982
- General, 1982
- Primaries, 1982
- Results, 1982
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 1982
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 1982
- U.S. House of Representatives - General, 1982
- U.S. Senate, 1982
- Virginia House of Delegates - 33rd, 1982
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th, 1982
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 1982
- Virginia House of Delegates - 36th, 1982
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 1982
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th, 1982
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 1982
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th, 1982
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 1982
- Virginia House of Delegates - 42nd, 1982
- Virginia House of Delegates - 43rd, 1982
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 1982
- Virginia House of Delegates - General, 1982
- Board of Supervisors - Annandale, 1983
- Board of Supervisors - Centreville, 1983
- Board of Supervisors - Chairman, 1983
- Board of Supervisors - Dranesville, 1983
- Board of Supervisors - Lee, 1983
- Board of Supervisors - Mason, 1983
- Board of Supervisors - Mount Vernon, 1983
- Board of Supervisors - Providence, 1983
- Board of Supervisors - Springfield, 1983
- Bonds, 1983
- Bonds - School - City of Fairfax, 1983
- Clerk of the Court, 1983
- Commonwealth's Attorney, 1983
- General, 1983
- Results, 1983
- Sheriff, 1983
- Virginia House of Delegates - 33rd, 1983
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th, 1983
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 1983
- Virginia House of Delegates - 36th, 1983
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 1983
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th, 1983
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 1983
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th, 1983
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 1983
- Virginia House of Delegates - 42nd, 1983
- Virginia House of Delegates - 43rd, 1983
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 1983
- Virginia House of Delegates - 46th, 1983
- Virginia House of Delegates - 47th, 1983
- Virginia State Senate - 30th, 1983
- Virginia State Senate - 32nd, 1983
- Virginia State Senate - 33rd, 1983
- Virginia State Senate - 34th, 1983
- Virginia State Senate - 35th, 1983
- Virginia State Senate - 36th, 1983
- Board of Supervisors - Mount Vernon - to fill seat, 1984
- Bonds, 1984
- Bonds - School Referndum, 1984
- City of Fairfax - Council, 1984
- City of Fairfax - Mayor, 1984
- Clifton - Council, 1984
- Clifton - Mayor, 1984
- General, 1984
- Herndon - Council, 1984
- Herndon - Mayor, 1984
- Primaries, 1984
- Results, 1984
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 1984
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 1984
- Vienna - Council, 1984
- Vienna - Mayor, 1984
- Board of Supervisors - Providence - Special Election, 1985
- Bonds, 1985
- Bonds - McLean Community Center, 1985
- Bonds - Roads, 1985
- Bonds - Water, 1985
- City of Fairfax - Council, 1985
- City of Fairfax - Mayor, 1985
- General, 1985
- Governor - Democratic Primary - Baliles, 1985
- Governor - Democratic Primary - Davis, 1985
- Governor - General, 1985
- Herndon, 1985
- Results, 1985
- Virginia House of Delegates - 33rd, 1985
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th, 1985
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 1985
- Virginia House of Delegates - 36th, 1985
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 1985
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th, 1985
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 1985
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th, 1985
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 1985
- Virginia House of Delegates - 42nd, 1985
- Virginia House of Delegates - 43rd, 1985
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 1985
- Virginia House of Delegates - 46th, 1985
- Virginia House of Delegates - 47th, 1985
- Vienna, 1985
- Bonds, 1986
- City of Fairfax - Council, 1986
- Clifton - Mayor and Council, 1986
- Constitution, 1986
- General, 1986
- Herndon - Council, 1986
- Herndon - Mayor, 1986
- Results, 1986
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 1986
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 1986
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 1986
- Vienna - Council, 1986
- Vienna - Mayor, 1986
- Board of Supervisors - Annandale, 1987
- Board of Supervisors - Centreville, 1987
- Board of Supervisors - Chairman, 1987
- Board of Supervisors - Dranesville, 1987
- Board of Supervisors - Lee, 1987
- Board of Supervisors - Mason, 1987
- Board of Supervisors - Mount Vernon, 1987
- Board of Supervisors - Providence, 1987
- Board of Supervisors - Springfield, 1987
- General, 1987
- Referendums - City of Fairfax, 1987
- Referendums - Lottery, 1987
- Results, 1987
- Sheriff, 1987
- Virginia House of Delegates - 33rd, 1987
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th, 1987
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 1987
- Virginia House of Delegates - 36th, 1987
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 1987
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th, 1987
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 1987
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th, 1987
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 1987
- Virginia House of Delegates - 42nd, 1987
- Virginia House of Delegates - 43rd, 1987
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 1987
- Virginia House of Delegates - 45th, 1987
- Virginia House of Delegates - 46th, 1987
- Virginia House of Delegates - 47th, 1987
- Virginia State Senate - 30th, 1987
- Virginia State Senate - 32nd, 1987
- Virginia State Senate - 34th, 1987
- Virginia State Senate - 35th, 1987
- Bonds - Human Services, 1988
- Bonds - Parks, 1988
- Bonds - Roads, 1988
- Bonds - Schools, 1988
- City of Fairfax - Council, 1988
- Referendums - Pari-Mutual, 1988
- Results, 1988
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 1988
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 1988
- U.S. Senate, 1988
- U.S. Senate - 30th, 1988
- Bonds, 1989
- General, 1989
- Governor, 1989
- Governor - Parris, 1989
- Governor - Wilder, 1989
- Referendums - Government Status, 1989
- Results, 1989
- Virginia House of Delegates - 33rd, 1989
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th, 1989
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 1989
- Virginia House of Delegates - 36th, 1989
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 1989
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38, 1989
- Virginia House of Delegates - 33rd, 1989
- Virginia House of Delegates - 33rd, 1989
- Virginia House of Delegates - 33rd, 1989
- Virginia House of Delegates - 33rd, 1989
- Virginia House of Delegates - 33rd, 1989
- Virginia House of Delegates - 33rd, 1989
- Virginia House of Delegates - 33rd, 1989
- Virginia House of Delegates - 33rd, 1989
- Vienna, 1989
- Bonds, 1990
- City of Fairfax, 1990
- General, 1990
- Referendums - Government and Status, 1990
- Results, 1990
- Sheriff, 1990
- Soil and Water Conservation District, 1990
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 1990
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 1990
- U.S. Senate, 1990
- Vienna, 1990
- Board of Supervisors - Braddock, 1991
- Board of Supervisors - Centreville, 1991
- Board of Supervisors - Chairman, 1991
- Board of Supervisors - Dranesville, 1991
- Clerk of the Court, 1991
- General, 1991
- Results, 1991
- Results - City of Fairfax, 1991
- Sheriff, 1991
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 1991
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 1991
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th, 1991
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 1991
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th, 1991
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 1991
- Virginia House of Delegates - 43rd, 1991
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 1991
- Virginia House of Delegates - 45th, 1991
- Virginia House of Delegates - 46th, 1991
- Virginia House of Delegates - 53rd, 1991
- Virginia House of Delegates - 67th, 1991
- Virginia State Senate - 32nd, 1991
- Virginia State Senate - 33rd, 1991
- Virginia State Senate - 35th, 1991
- Virginia State Senate - 36th, 1991
- Virginia State Senate - 37th, 1991
- Vienna, 1991
- Board of Supervisors - Lee, 1992
- Board of Supervisors - Mount Vernon, 1992
- Board of Supervisors - Providence, 1992
- Board of Supervisors - Springfield, 1992
- Board of Supervisors - Sully, 1992
- Bonds, 1992
- City of Fairfax - Commissioner of the Revenue, 1992
- City of Fairfax - Mayor/Town Council, 1992
- Clifton - Mayor/Town Council, 1992
- Gambling, 1992
- General, 1992
- Herndon - Mayor/City Council, 1992
- Referendum Package, 1992
- Results, 1992
- Soil and Water Conservation District, 1992
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 1992
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 1992
- U.S. House of Representatives - 11th - (folder 1 of 2), 1992
- U.S. House of Representatives - 11th - (folder 2 of 2), 1992
- U.S. House of Representatives - 33rd, 1992
- U.S. House of Representatives - 36th, 1992
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th, 1992
- Vienna - Mayor/Council, 1992
- Attorney General, 1993
- Bonds, 1993
- City of Fairfax, 1993
- General, 1993
- Governor, 1993
- Lieutenant Governor, 1993
- Referendums - School Board, 1993
- Results, 1993
- Soil and Water Conservation District, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 32nd, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 33rd, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 36th, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 42nd, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 43rd, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 45th, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 48th, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 53rd, 1993
- Virginia House of Delegates - 67th, 1993
- Vienna, 1993
- City of Fairfax, 1994
- General, 1994
- Results, 1994
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 1994
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 1994
- U.S. House of Representatives - 11th, 1994
- U.S. Senate, 1994
- U.S. Senate - August, 1994
- U.S. Senate - Democratic Primary, 1994
- U.S. Senate - Independents, 1994
- U.S. Senate - January-July, 1994
- U.S. Senate- November, 1994
- U.S. Senate -Republican Convention, 1994
- U.S. Senate - September, 1994
- Board of Supervisors - Braddock, 1995
- Board of Supervisors - Chairman, 1995
- Board of Supervisors - Dranesville, 1995
- Board of Supervisors - Hunter Mill, 1995
- Board of Supervisors - Lee, 1995
- Board of Supervisors - Mason, 1995
- Board of Supervisors - Mount Vernon, 1995
- Board of Supervisors - Providence, 1995
- Board of Supervisors - Springfield, 1995
- Board of Supervisors - Sully, 1995
- Commonwealth's Attorney, 1995
- General, 1995
- Results, 1995
- School Board, 1995
- School Board - Endorsements, 1995
- Sheriff, 1995
- Virginia House of Delegates - 33rd, 1995
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th, 1995
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 1995
- Virginia House of Delegates - 36th, 1995
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 1995
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th, 1995
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 1995
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th, 1995
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 1995
- Virginia House of Delegates - 42nd, 1995
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 1995
- Virginia House of Delegates - 45th, 1995
- Virginia House of Delegates - 48th, 1995
- Virginia House of Delegates - 53rd, 1995
- Virginia House of Delegates - 67th, 1995
- Virginia State Senate - 32nd, 1995
- Virginia State Senate - 33rd, 1995
- Virginia State Senate - 34th, 1995
- Virginia State Senate - 35th, 1995
- Virginia State Senate - 36th, 1995
- Vienna - Council, 1995
- Amendments - Constitutional, 1996
- City of Fairfax, 1996
- City of Fairfax - School Board, 1996
- General, 1996
- Results, 1996
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 1996
- U.S. House of Representatives - 11th, 1996
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 1996
- U.S. Senate, 1996
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th - Special Election, 1996
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th - Special Election, 1996
- Attorney General, 1997
- Bond Referendums - City of Fairfax, 1997
- Bonds - School - City of Fairfax, 1997
- City of Fairfax - Commissioner of the Revenue, 1997
- General, 1997
- Governor - (folder 1 of 2), 1997
- Governor - (folder 2 of 2), 1997
- Lieutenant Governor, 1997
- Results, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 32nd, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 36th, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 42nd, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 43rd, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 45th, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 47th, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 48th, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 53rd, 1997
- Virginia House of Delegates - 67th, 1997
- Bond Referendums, 1998
- City of Fairfax - Council, 1998
- City of Fairfax - Mayor, 1998
- City of Fairfax - School Board, 1998
- General, 1998
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 1998
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 1998
- U.S. House of Representatives - 11th, 1998
- Board of Supervisors, 1999
- Board of Supervisors - Braddock, 1999
- Board of Supervisors - Chairman, 1999
- Board of Supervisors - Dranesville, 1999
- Board of Supervisors - Hunter Mill, 1999
- Board of Supervisors - Lee, 1999
- Board of Supervisors - Mason, 1999
- Board of Supervisors - Providence, 1999
- Bonds, 1999
- C.W. Levy, 1999
- Clerk of the Court, 1999
- General, 1999
- Results, 1999
- School Board, 1999
- School Board - At Larger, 1999
- School Board - Braddock, 1999
- School Board - Hunter Mill, 1999
- School Board - Lee, 1999
- School Board - Mason, 1999
- School Board - Mount Vernon, 1999
- School Board - Providence, 1999
- School Board - Springfield, 1999
- Sheriff, 1999
- Soil and Water Conservation District, 1999
- Virginia House of Delegates, 1999
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 1999
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 1999
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th, 1999
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 1999
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th, 1999
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 1999
- Virginia House of Delegates - 43rd, 1999
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 1999
- Virginia House of Delegates - 45th, 1999
- Virginia House of Delegates - 48th, 1999
- Virginia House of Delegates - 53rd, 1999
- Virginia House of Delegates - 67th, 1999
- Virginia State Senate - 30th, 1999
- Virginia State Senate - 32nd, 1999
- Virginia State Senate - 33rd, 1999
- Virginia State Senate - 34th, 1999
- Virginia State Senate - 36th, 1999
- Virginia State Senate - General, 1999
- Voter Identification Program, 1999
- Ammendments - Constitutional, 2000
- General, 2000
- Results, 2000
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 2000
- U.S. Senate, 2000
- Attorney General, 2001
- Bonds - Schools, 2001
- City of Fairfax, 2001
- General, 2001
- Governor, 2001
- Lieutenant Governor, 2001
- Primaries - Democrat, 2001
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th, 2001
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 2001
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 2001
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th, 2001
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 2001
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 2001
- Virginia House of Delegates - 42nd, 2001
- Virginia House of Delegates - 43rd, 2001
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 2001
- Virginia House of Delegates - 86th, 2001
- Amendements - Constitutional, 2002
- Bonds, 2002
- City of Fairfax, 2002
- City of Fairfax - Council, 2002
- City of Fairfax - Mayor, 2002
- General, 2002
- Herndon, 2002
- Referendums - Transportation, 2002
- Results, 2002
- School Board, 2002
- School Board - Special Election, 2002
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 2002
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 2002
- U.S. House of Representatives - 11th, 2002
- U.S. Senate, 2002
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th - Special Election, 2002
- Virginia State Senate - 39th, 2002
- Vienna, 2002
- Voters' Guides, 2002
- Board of Supervisors - Braddock, 2003
- Board of Supervisors - Chairman, 2003
- Board of Supervisors - Dranesville, 2003
- Board of Supervisors - Hunter Mill, 2003
- Board of Supervisors - Lee, 2003
- Board of Supervisors - Mason, 2003
- Board of Supervisors - Mount Vernon, 2003
- Board of Supervisors - Springfield, 2003
- Board of Supervisors - Sully, 2003
- Commonwealth's Attorney, 2003
- General, 2003
- Primaries - Democrat, 2003
- Primaries - Republican, 2003
- Results, 2003
- School Board, 2003
- Sheriff, 2003
- Soil and Water Conservation District, 2003
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 2003
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 2003
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th, 2003
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 2003
- Virginia House of Delegates - 42nd, 2003
- Virginia House of Delegates - 43rd, 2003
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 2003
- Virginia House of Delegates - 45th, 2003
- Virginia House of Delegates - 49th, 2003
- Virginia House of Delegates - 53rd, 2003